{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":null},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"733","name":"Gold Coast","address":"2971 E Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48234","owner":"Dennis Rabchun","licenseNumber":"075131","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","coords":"-83.07254,42.43312","geojson":{"id":"733","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.072536069,42.4331247760001]},"properties":{"name":"Gold Coast","owner":"Dennis Rabchun","address":"2971 E Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48234","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"075131","establishmentid":"733","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"365.0","most_recent_license_date":"4/27/2016"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"1751","name":"Ambiance","address":"2959 E Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"488","name":"Deluxe Coney Island","address":"2923 E Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"1139","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #648","address":"2928 E Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48211"},{"establishmentid":"51622580","name":"The New  Conant Street Grill","address":"19132 Conant St","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"51622584","name":"Conant St. Grill","address":"19132 Conant ","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"337","name":"Happy's Pizza #2","address":"2855 E Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"1398","name":"Asian Corned Beef","address":"2847 E Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"3621","name":"Nunn's Bar-B-Que Restaurant II","address":"19196 Conant Ave","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"1911","name":"United Grill Coney Island of Detroit","address":"18801 Conant St","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"3072","name":"Munchee's Mania","address":"19310 Conant Ave","zipcode":"48234"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43629","inspectionDate":"2018-09-06T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not stored in self-draining position","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store in self-draining position."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"39664","inspectionDate":"2017-08-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-08-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not stored in self-draining position","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store in self-draining position."},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"gnats","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."},{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \r\n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \r\n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \r\n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \r\n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\r\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \r\n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \r\n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\r\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\r\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\r\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\r\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\r\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) used for nonpotentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as required above."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All of the following food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American national standards institute, utilizing the conference for food protection standards:  (a) A food service establishment that is not any of the following:    (i) Operating under a temporary food service establishment license.  (ii) A vending machine location.     (b) An extended retail food establishment.  (c) Operated within a retail grocery.  (2) An individual certified under subsection (1) shall be recognized with full faith and credit by the state and all local units of government throughout the state.  (3) The department may promulgate rules to do all of the following:  (a) Develop requirements for retail food establishments to follow when employing certified food safety managers or personnel.  (b) Set a reasonable date for compliance with the requirements under subdivision (a) taking into consideration existing local personnel certification requirements.  (c) Establish certification fees necessary to implement, maintain, and track certified individuals directly or by contract. The department may annually adjust the schedule of fees to provide that the fee charged is sufficient to cover the cost of the certification tracking program.  (d) Implement and enforce the requirements described in subdivision (a).    (4) The certification program developed by the American national standards institute, as it exists on April 1, 2008 , is incorporated by reference. The department may adopt updates to the certification program accreditation standards in subsection (1) by rule.     (5) This section does not prohibit any local legislative body from implementing a food handler program, an employee health certification program, or a manager certification program, if it is not in conflict with this section.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide manufacture lable "},{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not covered","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep covered."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"733"}}